import { v4 as uuid } from "uuid";

export const questions = [
  {
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "DBMS",
    question: "What is the full form of DBMS?",
    optionA: "Data of Binary Management System",
    optionB: "b) Database Management System",
    optionC: "Database Management Service",
    optionD:  "Data Backup Management System",
    answer:"Database Management System",
    categoryName: "DBMS",
  },
  {
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "DSA",
    question: "2. What is a database?",
    optionA: "DBMS is a collection of queries",
    optionB: "b) DBMS is a high-level language",
    optionC: "DBMS is a programming language",
    optionD:  "DBMS stores, modifies and retrieves data",
    answer: "DBMS stores, modifies and retrieves data",
    categoryName: "DBMS",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "JAVA",
    question: "3. Who created the first DBMS?",
    optionA: "Edgar Frank Codd",
    optionB: "b) Charles Bachman",
    optionC: "Charles Babbage",
    optionD:  "Sharon B. Codd",
    answer: "Charles Bachman",
    categoryName: "DBMS",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "OOPS",
    question: "4.  Which of the following is not a type of database?",
    optionA: "Hierarchical",
    optionB: "Network",
    optionC:  "Distributed",
    optionD:   "Decentralized",
    answer:"Decentralized",
    categoryName: "DBMS",
  },
  {
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "DSA",
    question: "5. Which type of data can be stored in the database?",
    optionA: "Image oriented data",
    optionB: "Text, files containing data",
    optionC: "c) Data in the form of audio or video",
    optionD:  "All of the above",
    answer:" All of the above",
    categoryName: "DBMS",
  },
//   Question data set of DSA
  {
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "DSA",
    question: "The data structure required for Breadth First Traversal on a graph is?",
    optionA: "Stack",
    optionB: "Array",
    optionC: "Queue",
    optionD:  "Tree",
    answer:"Queue",
    categoryName: "DSA",
  },
  {
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "DSA",
    question: "A queue follows __________",
    optionA: "FIFO (First In First Out) principle",
    optionB: "LIFO (Last In First Out) principle",
    optionC: "Ordered array",
    optionD:  "Linear tree",
    answer:"FIFO (First In First Out) principle",
    categoryName: "DSA",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "DSA",
    question: "Circular Queue is also known as ________",
    optionA: "Ring Buffer",
    optionB: "Square Buffer",
    optionC: "Rectangle Buffer",
    optionD:  "Curve Buffer",
    answer:"Ring Buffer",
    categoryName: "DSA",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "DSA",
    question: "Queues serve major role in ______________",
    optionA: "Simulation of recursion",
    optionB: "Simulation of arbitrary linked list",
    optionC: "Simulation of limited resource allocation",
    optionD:  "Simulation of heap sort",
    answer:"Simulation of limited resource allocation",
    categoryName: "DSA",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "DSA",
    question: "Which of the following is not the type of queue?",
    optionA: "Ordinary queue",
    optionB: "Single ended queue",
    optionC: "Circular queue",
    optionD:  "Priority queue",
    answer: "Single ended queue",
    categoryName: "DSA",
  },
//   Question data set of JAVA
{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "JAVA",
    question: "Who invented Java Programming?",
    optionA: "Guido van Rossum",
    optionB: "James Gosling",
    optionC: "Dennis Ritchie",
    optionD:  "Bjarne Stroustrup",
    answer: "James Gosling",
    categoryName: "JAVA",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "JAVA",
    question: "Which statement is true about Java?",
    optionA: "Java is a sequence-dependent programming language",
    optionB: " Java is a code dependent programming language",
    optionC: "Java is a platform-dependent programming language",
    optionD:  "Java is a platform-independent programming language",
    answer: "Java is a platform-independent programming language",
    categoryName: "JAVA",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "JAVA",
    question: "Which component is used to compile, debug and execute the java programs?",
    optionA: "JRE",
    optionB: "JIT",
    optionC: "JDK",
    optionD: "JVM",
    answer: "JDK",
    categoryName: "JAVA",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "JAVA",
    question: "Which one of the following is not a Java feature?",
    optionA: "Object-oriented",
    optionB: "Use of pointers",
    optionC: "Portable",
    optionD:  "Dynamic and Extensible",
    answer: "Use of pointers",
    categoryName: "JAVA",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "JAVA",
    question: "Which of these cannot be used for a variable name in Java?",
    optionA: "identifier & keyword",
    optionB: "identifier",
    optionC: "keyword",
    optionD:  "none of the mentioned",
    answer: "keyword",
    categoryName: "JAVA",
  },
//   Question data set of OOPS
{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "OOPS",
    question: "Who invented OOP?",
    optionA: "Andrea Ferro",
    optionB: "Adele Goldberg",
    optionC: "Alan Kay",
    optionD:  "Dennis Ritchie",
    answer: "Alan Kay",
    categoryName: "OOPS",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "OOPS",
    question: "Which is not a feature of OOP in general definitions?",
    optionA: "Efficient Code",
    optionB: "Code reusability",
    optionC: "Modularity",
    optionD:  "Duplicate/Redundant data",
    answer: "Duplicate/Redundant data",
    categoryName: "OOPS",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "OOPS",
    question: "When OOP concept did first came into picture?",
    optionA: "1980’s",
    optionB: "1995",
    optionC: "1970’s",
    optionD:  "1993",
    answer: "1970’s",
    categoryName: "OOPS",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "OOPS",
    question: "Which feature of OOP indicates code reusability?",
    optionA: "Abstraction",
    optionB: "Polymorphism",
    optionC: "Encapsulation",
    optionD:  "Inheritance",
    answer: "Inheritance",
    categoryName: "OOPS",
  },{
    _id: uuid(),
    title: "OOPS",
    question: "Which among the following doesn’t come under OOP concept?",
    optionA: "Data hiding",
    optionB: "Message passing",
    optionC: "Platform independent",
    optionD:  "Data binding",
    answer: "Platform independent",
    categoryName: "OOPS",
  },

]